masterseek.com 2006-04-27

# Masterseek-Business directory-Business search engine-company directory

### Masterseek Privacy Policy 

Internet user privacy is of high importance to Masterseek and our clients. We support the protection of client and consumers' privacy rights as a fundamental element of our business.

Respect for customer privacy is the core value of our services. Far from limiting the marketer's options, the boundaries of privacy establish a space of opportunity, if obeyed. Messages that remain in accord with these boundaries will frequently find receptive customers. Masterseek's rigorous permission-based privacy policy is designed to ensure that visitors to our website understand how and why Masterseek may collect and use information provided by users.

Masterseek is committed to protecting the privacy of users of the Masterseek Web site. The information we collect is used exclusively to facilitate services that we provide to you. We value your privacy and will take all necessary steps to protect it.

We support the Fair Information Practice Principles of Notice, Choice, Access, and Security. The following document thoroughly explains our privacy policy. Please read it carefully. If you have any questions, please contact [ Privacy](mailto:privacy@masterseek.com)

**Data collected**    
We collect information about how you browse thorough our website. We gather general information about your operating system, web browser and language. We also give our visitors the opportunity to subscribe to our Newsletter. In order to subscribe to our newsletter, we collect personal information and email address and preferences. Visitors are also able to check out our online demo gallery. In order to demonstrate our online demos, we must collect personal information and email address in order to provide a personalized experienced in our campaigns. If you want to contact us via our feedback form, we collect personal information, business information, contact information and your questions/comment.

Masterseek does not collect personal data that international laws consider "sensitive." That is, we do not collect information about an individual's medical condition, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership or sexual life.

We also do not knowingly collect information from children.

**Advertisers / Membership profiles**

In order to advertise on Masterseek or signup for one of our Memberships, we will ask you to provide us with following data: Company information, contact information, name and email on contact person, type of membership and for some companies VAT registration. Credit Card information ARE NOT collected and stored at Masterseek after processing your online payment. Please refer to [ www.dibs.dk](http://www.dibs.dk/1764.0.html) for details about the secure internet payment used on Masterseek.

**Cookies**

Masterseek uses cookies to remember you on our website.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. When this information is stored on your hard drive, our system is able to recognize your browser and in turn customize Web page content and services for you. Cookies are used by [ www.masterseek.com](http://www.masterseek.com/) so that we can remember our previous interactions with you and make it easier for you to access our Web site. Cookies only contain an id so we know if you are a repeated visitor.

**Your Opt-Out**

Masterseek will not sell, transfer, assign or rent your customer information to any third party without your permission, unless required by law. In the unlikely event that Masterseek changes this policy, we will provide advance notice.

Our newsletter subscribers can anytime unsubscribe/Opt Out from our service.

Information collected on online demos, will never be shared with any third party. Masterseek might contact you to collect your viewpoints on our online demos.

**Surveys**

From time-to-time, our site may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary, so the user has a choice whether or not to disclose the information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code, occupation). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Third parties - Advertisers**

No information is shared with any third parties or third party advertisers. In the unlikely event that Masterseek changes this policy, we will provide advance notice.

**Log files**

We use IP addresses and cookies to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links**

We use email links located on the website to allow users to contact us directly with any questions or comments they may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly. We use the information collected to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file user comments to improve the site and program, or review and discard the information. Users' personal information is only shared with third parties to fulfil service requests made by the user and in the situations described above.

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Masterseek is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Masterseek.

**Security and Enforcement**

Masterseek protects your information from loss, misuse, alteration, or unauthorized disclosure by requiring employees with access to personal data to comply with our privacy policy.

Masterseek understands the importance of security for those who visit our Web site. We only disclose customer data to those parties who help us deliver services to you, such as the companies provide our Internet website and related services. We also require them to comply with our Privacy Policy.

In addition, Masterseek employees who have access to customer data are required to comply with this Privacy Policy. Any employee who violates or abuses the Masterseek's privacy practices is subject to disciplinary action, including termination of employment and may be subject to legal proceedings.

In order to assure you that Masterseek adheres to these privacy principles, Masterseek takes several steps. First, questions or complaints can be directed to our Headquarter in New York, USA.

If you have questions, concerns or complaints about Masterseek's Privacy Policy or practices, you may contact:

**Masterseek Corp.**  
Att: User Privacy  
Head office Masterseek Corp.  
82, Wall Street   
10005, New York   
USA
